我叫麦克斯
I'm Max.
当你的瞳孔消失时  是代表什么意思
Uh, what does it mean when you don't have pupils?
你们真是太萌了
You guys are so cute.
我知道你们还没看过这部电影
Oh, I know you haven't seen the movie,
所以我简单告诉你们一下剧情
so I'll give you a quick rundown of what happens
好应付媒体提问
for press questions.
我看看  你损失所有财产
Uh, let's see. You lose your money.
惨惨惨  然后你遇到她
Sad, sad, sad. And then you meet this one.
惨惨惨
Sad, sad, sad.
你真是太萌了
You are so cute.
电影已经不单纯只是说你们两个了
It's not as much about the two of you anymore.
故事情节有点拉拉味儿
The storyline came off a little lesbionic,
坦白说  挺去年的炒作法
which is kinda last year.
我也有点拉拉味儿
I just came off a little lesbionic.
有小妞一直不停打电话找我
Maggie won't stop calling me.
天啊
Oh, my God.
苔丝来了  她真是完美无瑕
There's Tess. Oh, she's flawless.